var _slicedToArray=function(){function a(a,b){var c,d=[],e=!0,f=!1;try{for(var g,h=a[Symbol.iterator]();!(e=(g=h.next()).done)&&(d.push(g.value),!(b&&d.length===b));e=!0);}catch(a){f=!0,c=a}finally{try{!e&&h["return"]&&h["return"]()}finally{if(f)throw c}}return d}return function(b,c){if(Array.isArray(b))return b;if(Symbol.iterator in Object(b))return a(b,c);throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to destructure non-iterable instance")}}(),NUMQUESTIONS=10,questionsMap=new Map,quizSequence=[],quizStats={counter:0,correct:0,wrong:0,currentQuestion:0};function quizQuestions(){questionsMap.set(1,{question:"\u767B\u8A18\u6216\u9810\u7D04\u4F7F\u7528\u672C\u9928\u96FB\u8166\uFF0C\u9700\u651C\u5E36\u4EC0\u9EBC\u6771\u897F?",a:"\u9EA5\u7576\u52DE",b:"\u624B\u6A5F",c:"\u672C\u4EBA\u501F\u95B1\u8B49\u6216\u6709\u6548\u8EAB\u5206\u8B49\u660E\u6587\u4EF6",answer:"c"}),questionsMap.set(2,{question:"\u516C\u7528\u96FB\u8166\u6BCF\u6B21\u4F7F\u7528\u70BA\u591A\u4E45?",a:"\u4E00\u500B\u79AE\u62DC",b:"\u4E00\u5929",c:" \u4E09\u5341\u5206\u9418",answer:"c"}),questionsMap.set(3,{question:"fun\u5FC3\u807D\u6545\u4E8B\u6642\u9593\u548C\u597D\u73A9\u7684\u5EF6\u4F38\u6D3B\u52D5\u6642\u9593\uFF0C\u662F\u79AE\u62DC\u5E7E\u4E0A\u534810\u9EDE\u523011\u9EDE?",a:"\u79AE\u62DC\u4E00",b:"\u79AE\u62DC\u516D",c:"\u79AE\u62DC\u4E8C",answer:"b"}),questionsMap.set(4,{question:"\u770B\u5B8C\u66F8\u8981\u600E\u9EBC\u505A?",a:"\u5C07\u66F8\u672C\u9001\u56DE\u4ED6\u7684\u5BB6",b:"\u4E82\u4E1F\u5728\u5730\u4E0A",c:"\u5168\u90E8\u5E36\u56DE\u5BB6",answer:"a"}),questionsMap.set(5,{question:"\u54FA\u96C6\u4E73\u5BA4\u662F\u7528\u4F86\u505A\u4EC0\u9EBC\u7684?",a:"\u54FA\u4E73",b:"\u770B\u66F8",c:"\u7761\u89BA",answer:"a"}),questionsMap.set(6,{question:"\u958B\u67B6\u95B1\u89BD\u5340\u6709\u4F55\u7A2E\u66F8\u7C4D?",a:"\u81EA\u7136\u79D1\u5B78",b:"\u793E\u6703\u79D1\u5B78",c:"\u4EE5\u4E0A\u7686\u662F",answer:"c"}),questionsMap.set(7,{question:"\u95B1\u89BD\u5340\u6574\u9AD4\u7A7A\u9593\u8A2D\u8A08\u5982\u4F55?",a:"\u5F88\u72F9\u7A84",b:"\u5BEC\u655E\u660E\u4EAE\u8996\u91CE\u901A\u900F",c:"\u5F88\u6697\u90FD\u6C92\u958B\u71C8",answer:"b"}),questionsMap.set(8,{question:"\u967D\u5149\u975C\u8B80\u5340\u90A3\u4E9B\u5730\u65B9\u6709\u5225\u65BC\u4E00\u822C\u7684\u95B1\u89BD\u5EA7\u4F4D?",a:"\u53EF\u9CE5\u77B0\u5E02\u5340\u4E26\u4EAB\u53D7\u5BA4\u5167\u7DA0\u610F",b:"\u8DDF\u4E00\u822C\u7684\u95B1\u89BD\u5EA7\u4F4D\u76F8\u540C",c:"\u61F6\u5F97\u6BD4\u8F03",answer:"a"}),questionsMap.set(9,{question:"\u591A\u529F\u80FD\u6559\u5BA4\u5167\u90E8\u8A2D\u5099\u9664\u8AB2\u684C\u6905\u5916\uFF0C\u9084\u5099\u6709\u4EC0\u9EBC\u8A2D\u5099?",a:"\u6295\u5F71\u6A5F",b:"\u6578\u4F4D\u5316\u591A\u529F\u80FD\u8B1B\u684C",c:"\u4EE5\u4E0A\u7686\u662F",answer:"c"}),questionsMap.set(10,{question:"\u591A\u529F\u80FD\u6559\u5BA4\u6BCF\u5E74\u5747\u8209\u8FA6\u8A31\u591A\u8AB2\u7A0B\u6D3B\u52D5\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u5305\u62EC\u4EC0\u9EBC?",a:"\u591A\u5143\u6587\u5316\u8AB2\u7A0B",b:"\u89AA\u5B50\u5171\u8B80",c:"\u4EE5\u4E0A\u7686\u662F",answer:"c"})}var questionContainer=document.getElementById("the-question"),answerA=document.getElementById("a"),answerB=document.getElementById("b"),answerC=document.getElementById("c"),scoreCounter=document.getElementById("score-counter");function determineSequence(){var a,b=!0,c=!1;try{for(var d,e=questionsMap[Symbol.iterator]();!(b=(d=e.next()).done);b=!0){var f=d.value,g=_slicedToArray(f,2),h=g[0],i=g[1];quizSequence.push(h)}}catch(b){c=!0,a=b}finally{try{!b&&e.return&&e.return()}finally{if(c)throw a}}quizSequence=function(a){for(var b,c,d=a.length;0!==d;)c=Math.floor(Math.random()*d),d-=1,b=a[d],a[d]=a[c],a[c]=b;return a}(quizSequence)}function getNextQuestion(){quizStats.counter++;var d=quizSequence.shift(),e=questionsMap.get(d).a,a=questionsMap.get(d).b,b=questionsMap.get(d).c,c=questionsMap.get(d).question;questionContainer.textContent=c,answerA.textContent=e,answerB.textContent=a,answerC.textContent=b,quizStats.currentQuestion=d}function addEventListeners(){answerA.addEventListener("click",checkTheAnswer),answerB.addEventListener("click",checkTheAnswer),answerC.addEventListener("click",checkTheAnswer)}function addDataAttributes(){answerA.setAttribute("data-answer","a"),answerB.setAttribute("data-answer","b"),answerC.setAttribute("data-answer","c")}function checkTheAnswer(){var a=this.dataset.answer,b=questionsMap.get(quizStats.currentQuestion).answer;a===b?(quizStats.correct++,this.classList.add("correct")):(quizStats.wrong++,this.classList.add("wrong"),document.getElementById(b).classList.add("correct")),scoreCounter.textContent=quizStats.correct,quizStats.counter<NUMQUESTIONS?(setTimeout(clearClasses,2e3),setTimeout(getNextQuestion,2e3)):showTheResults()}function clearClasses(){answerA.classList.remove("correct","wrong"),answerB.classList.remove("correct","wrong"),answerC.classList.remove("correct","wrong")}function showTheResults(){var a=document.getElementById("num-correct"),b=document.getElementById("num-wrong"),c=document.getElementById("num-total"),d=quizStats.correct,e=quizStats.wrong;a.textContent=d,b.textContent=e,c.textContent=NUMQUESTIONS,document.getElementsByClassName("results-container")[0].style.display="flex";const f=document.getElementById("result-desc");console.log(d),f.innerText=10==d?"\u53EB\u6211\u7B2C\u4E00\u540D\uFF01":10>d&&7<d?"\u5FEB\u6EFF\u5206\u4E86\uFF01\u518D\u52A0\u6CB9\uFF01\uFF01":7>=d&&4<d?"\u518D\u63A5\u518D\u53B2\uFF01":4>=d&&2<d?"\u8981\u518D\u52A0\u6CB9\u56C9\uFF01":"\u8981\u505A\u500B\u4E56\u5BF6\u5BF6\u54E6\uFF01"}(function(){quizQuestions(),determineSequence(),getNextQuestion(),addEventListeners(),addDataAttributes()})();var ok=function(){document.getElementsByClassName("results-container")[0].style.display="none",quizStats={counter:0,correct:0,wrong:0,currentQuestion:0},quizQuestions(),determineSequence(),getNextQuestion(),addEventListeners(),addDataAttributes(),clearClasses(),console.log("yoooooo")};